Excuse me. Chief Woo.
What is it?
Please take a look at this.
This is a report on the six hunters
who died in a C-rank dungeon.
The survivors are a D-rank hunter
and an E-rank hunter.
They must have escaped.
It happens all the time.
No. they didn't escape.
they got away by killing
the boss in the dungeon.
The D-rank hunter Yoo Jinho
had quite expensive equipment.
It's not surprising they managed to kill...
What are you trying to say?
Investigate it yourself
if you think it's suspicious.
No...
One of the survivors
is the survivor from the double dungeon.
Hunter Sung Jinwoo.
Sung Jinwoo?
And one of the six who died
is Hunter Hwang Dongsuk.
The brother of Hunter Hwang Dongsoo?
Then it is indeed concerning...
I'm back.
Welcome home.
A gift?
It's fried chicken.
Did something good happen?
I'm not sure if it's a good thing.
I've saved up for Mom's medical bills
and our living expenses.
My stingy brother
is actually spending money.
Oh. right.
What happened last time?
The raid mission.
They paid you a lot. right?
But you didn't seem to have any injuries.
Your companions must be strong.
Well. yeah.
You guys killed the enemies easily. right?
Yes. easily.
Regardless of the difference in strength.
at that moment. I had no hesitation.
Moreover. I didn't even despise them.
If it were the old me.
I would have tried to run away.
Has my bravery increased with my level?
But my opponents aren't magic beasts.
They are people.
Brother?
Are you okay?
I thought the clerk didn't give me
the change. but I was mistaken.
What?
Seriously. don't scare me.
Don't think about that now.
I must keep getting
stronger for my family.
And I mustn't die.
If the same thing happens again.
I will do just the same.
What is this?
"Harmful substance..."
It's detoxifying me?
I'm full.
You're done eating?
Then I'll eat it all up.
Then don't complain about getting fat.
I can't get drunk at all.
The system's special ability
has broken down the alcohol.
Is it the effect of some skill?
"Blessing..."
"Health and longevity..."
"Injuries and immunity..."
This is it.
The reward for the double dungeon mission.
So much has happened.
so I never bothered to check.
Is this why my limbs could regenerate?
There are many things I'm unclear about.
Brother.
Someone named Yoo Jinho called for you.
I'll be right there.
You've had too much to drink.
Alcohol is poison to the body.
I'm fine.
Even if I became a doctor.
I wouldn't treat you.
Sorry for suddenly calling you out.
I didn't expect to see you again.
I'm really happy.
You saved me after all. Jinwoo.
Thanks for giving me the magic gem too.
You helped a lot.
And.
you didn't reveal what happened.
Well. they tried
to kill us first. didn't they?
It was self-defense.
So. why did you want me?
I plan to build an attack team...
I refuse.
Huh? Well...
At least hear me out first.
I'm not interested
in hanging out with a rich guy.
Twenty missions! No...
Just 19 missions!
Nineteen missions?
You want to be a guild master?
Please let me finish first.
Please.
Go on then.
Yes.
As you speculated.
I want to obtain a guild master's license.
And one of the conditions
is to participate
in 20 raid missions as a hunter.
The last mission was my first one.
To take over the company.
I've studied hard.
I'm confident about the written exam.
But...
The real combat...
Aren't you the second young master
of Yoojin Construction?
I'm also doing this for our company.
Honestly. my father
wants to establish a guild.
Yoojin Construction
wants to establish a guild?
Yes.
Dungeons are certainly dangerous.
but they contain many rare treasures.
Magic gems and mana crystals
are just a part of it.
The bodies of high-rank beasts
can be used as materials for equipment.
One can say that everything
in the dungeon can be monetized.
You plan to have your own hunters conquer
the dungeons and take all the spoils.
so as to establish
a self-sufficient system?
That's right.
My father plans to hire
an S-rank hunter to be the guild master
and my brother as the vice-guild master
to run the guild like a company.
An S-rank hunter?
There are only seven of them nationally.
Yes.
Moreover. Min Byung-gu.
the only one who hasn't joined a guild.
has already retired.
Are you planning
to poach from other guilds?
I advise you not to do that.
The guilds that you poach from
will give you trouble.
My brother is not one of the Awakened.
so he can't be the guild master.
So you want to gain experience
and become the guild master
to compete with your brother?
If you want to hide your power
and participate in missions.
you will need companions.
Rather than teaming up
with high-ranked hunters.
completing the raid missions
with an E-rank hunter
would be more convincing to my father.
He is at least B-rank...
No. it might even be higher.
Teaming up with the wrong one
could be fatal.
But if it's him...
Take a look at this.
This building is planned
to be the guild's office.
It's currently valued at 30 billion.
This is the reward I am offering you.
Thirty billion for 19 C-rank missions.
Before. I would have accepted right away.
But...
If I'm the only one in the world who can
level up. that's a different story.
If I keep developing like this.
someday I will be S-rank...
No. maybe even higher than that.
In that case. 30 billion seems trivial.
More importantly. teaming up with people
without understanding
the impact of leveling up
is too risky.
Sorry.
Please. wait.
As long as you help me.
I will keep this secret for you
for a lifetime.
I want the information
on those two survivors.
Bring me their documents immediately.
Excuse me.
I have brought the documents.
Mr. Hwang.
My brother was killed.
This has not been confirmed yet...
The documents?
Yes. right here.
Laura.
what would happen
if I killed someone in another country?
Are you serious?
In a country with an extradition treaty
regarding hunter crimes.
you would be prosecuted
under that country's laws.
But if there's no extradition treaty.
you would be subject
to the laws of our own country.
So...
Depending on negotiations
with the government.
there might be leniency.
Adjust my schedule.
A sudden change of schedule
will affect the operation of the guild.
What's my schedule like?
It's fully booked for now.
Then clear it for later.
I understand.
I will arrange it.
D-rank Hunter Yoo Jinho.
E-rank Hunter Sung Jinwoo.
Don't die before then.
It's rare to see you exercising.
Studying all the time
is harmful to health. right?
Not because you had
too much fried chicken?
Hey.
If you had 30 billion. what would you do?
Why are you asking?
Just a random question.
Pay Mom's medical bills
and college tuition fees.
And the rest?
Save it up.
I don't know. That's too much money.
That's true.
Just keep up at your own pace.
Wait. brother!
Even as an E-rank one.
he is still a hunter.
Yes...
No. don't check.
Eleven kilometers?
Why are the numbers exceeding
the goal also recorded?
I see.
Then let's see how far I can go.
Brother...
I finally caught up.
I'll have another lap.
It stopped at twice the goal.
Then the rest...
The daily quest became the secret quest.
Yes.
I can choose different boxes.
Guess I'll choose Blessed Random Loot Box.
A key again?
"The Demon's Castle..."
Acquisition difficulty of an S-rank?!
"Cures all illnesses with powerful magic."
"Elixir of Life."
If that Elixir of Life
can really cure all illnesses...
Then of course...
If the acquisition difficulty of the key
is proportional to the dungeon's.
I am opening an S-rank dungeon.
If so.
what awaits me inside will be magic beasts
similar to those on Jeju Island
that even S-rank hunters can't handle.
With my current strength.
can I deal with beasts of that level?
It'd be a lie to say I'm not scared.
If things don't go well.
I will use this teleportation stone
I got from the Instance dungeon.
If I give up. everything is over.
I need to become stronger.
to level up even higher.
I must take back everything.
How could I die here?
I can hardly inflict any damage.
The gap is still so huge
after I use the title skills?
No use.
A warning?
A third of my HP was gone in an instant.
All abilities doubled?
So fast...
Only a half left?
There's no other way.
Full Recovery!
I stabbed it.
The warnings keep popping up.
The system issues warnings
at critical moments to prevent my death
because I am a player?
No matter what. this thing
can't be an ordinary second awakening.
I must hold on for at least
three minutes until its skill ends...
No. this is too dangerous.
Do I have to resort to this...
What can I do to survive?
A few more hits and I'll be dead.
Is there any way...
The shop...
I completely forgot.
One bottle costs 300 gold coins...
Three bottles.
One bottle only restores 100 points of HP?
This is simply...
Poison?
You've had too much to drink.
Alcohol is poison to the body.
I'm fine.
I have to do this.
Okay.
It's not over yet!
I can still move!
Its skill effect has ended!
Is this the item I obtained?
Another key?
Is this the door
that Cerberus was guarding?
What is this?
"The pattern for the Elixir of Life"?
This experience made me understand
my current strength.
Entering the castle at my current level
would surely mean death.
But...
I will return in the near future.
Definitely.